games4games.net 2011-09-27

# Games for Games - Privacy Policy

We respect your privacy and we are committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at our site The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site. Log Files Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track userÃ¢ï¿½ï¿½s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. Cookies A cookie is a piece of data stored on the userÃ¢ï¿½ï¿½s computer tied to information about the user. Our site donÃ¢ï¿½ï¿½t use cookies. However, Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. Links This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. Advertisers We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. We work with the ad companies. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies. Contact Information If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us [admin@games4games.net](mailto:admin@games4games.net)  

We Do Not allow any illegal or Copy righted Content,such as : Cracked Softwares,Movies,or Music , In OUR WEB SITE. **Please if you see any of those in one of our pages** contact us [admin@games4games.net](mailto:admin@games4games.net) **, So we can take a quick action**
